Yoo Min-ho, a suspect
in the murder of Kim Se-hee,
was released today
after the arrest warrant
was invalidated.
Yoo's marriage to a daughter
of Na-in Group, Lee Ji-yeon
made headlines,
but he is said
to have been having an affair
with the slain Ms. Kim.
The prosecution hopes
to acquire more evidence
and get a new warrant,
while Mr. Yoo is considering
his options for a defense lawyer.
Hello?
Yes. I will leave right away.
(Manager Han)
(Continue driving
to Bellagio Hotel?)
(No)
(So Ji-sup)
(Kim Yun-jin)
(Choe Gwang-il)
(Nana)
(Written and Directed
by Yun Jong-seok)
(Confession)
(Record of Vehicles Entering Time)
(License No.)
(No Entry - Private Property)
You have reached your destination.
Mr. Yoo Min-ho?
I am Attorney Yang Shin-ae.
Hello.
Attorney Jang called me.
He said you were hurrying over.
I was heading to the hotel
when I received
some new information.
It could not wait
until our meeting in the morning.
Can I come in?
Thanks.
I guess Attorney Jang is busy.
He will come after finishing up.
This way.
This was far for you to come
after an all-night interrogation.
I had to escape the press.
You have not escaped
the prosecution, though.
Police are stationed 5 minutes
from here.
(Attorney Yang Shin-ae)
Is coffee okay?
Is this
the Chairman's family cabin?
It used to be.
His wife's family grave
was nearby,
but since it was moved,
no one comes.
Just me sometimes,
to clear my head.
Thank you for taking
on the defense.
Let me be clear.
I will decide whether to do it
after hearing the whole story,
and...
what you should be grateful for
is the Chairman.
I never imagined the warrant
would be nullified.
The prosecution obtained
game-changing evidence.
A new arrest warrant could be
issued at dawn.
Arrest warrant?
But I did not kill her.
The prosecution thinks
differently.
What do you think?
There are too many holes
in your testimony.
Let's hear it from the beginning.
How long were you seeing
Kim Se-hee?
For a year and a half,
but it ended last fall.
Then why meet her again?
I received a blackmail threat
that morning.
I had to pay $1 million,
or they would reveal the affair.
I did not have that much on me,
but I took what I had.
Checking in?
Room 514, please.
Your guest has already gone up
to the room.
I did not expect both of us
to be under the same threat.
They told us to wait
in the room.
So we did.
Had you gone there
with Kim Se-hee before?
No.
Why did they call you
to such a far-off place?
Does that matter?
You must explain all the details
to get an innocent verdict.
Why didn't you report it?
The affair was already over,
and I did not want my wife
to know.
Did you think
you had a lot to lose?
I never thought that way.
Please continue.
We waited for about an hour.
What is going on?
Something is not right.
Let's go!
When I woke up,
I heard knocking.
Excuse me, sir?
Are you in there?
Sir, this is the police.
Please open the door.
This is the police.
Open the door!
We are responding to a call.
Are you in there?
Se-hee! Se-hee!
Se-hee, wake up.
Help!
Se-hee...
Freeze!
Hands up!
Move slowly.
Slowly, come out of there.
Come out!
It was not me.
- I did not do this.
- Step outside!
- Don't move!
- It was not me.
- Someone else was here!
Stay still!
Don't move!
Another person is here!
According to police records,
a housekeeper was outside
Room 514 at that time,
but she did not see anyone
exit the room.
Plus, it is impossible to come out
with the keychain locked.
So the only place left is
the balcony,
But that too was locked
from the inside.
They checked
every possible means of entry,
and found nothing.
The police see this
as a closed-door crime,
so if your testimony is true,
did the criminal simply vanish?
I don't know.
And how did he get in?
Must have been inside already.
Someone framed me.
Who?
I don't know.
The police should catch him.
You need more than intelligence
to create good testimony.
You need creativity.
Your testimony has no creativity.
I am telling the truth.
Why do I need creativity?
With that testimony,
you are the only one
who saw a third person.
You are obviously the criminal.
Ms. Yang.
It was not me.
I did not do it.
(Manager Han)
Hello?
Is it confirmed?
Yes.
Okay, then.
I found out
what the new evidence is.
A witness at the crime scene.
Is that possible?
You called it a closed-door crime.
That is right.
There can't be any witnesses
to Kim Se-hee's murder.
Then what crime did this
new witness see?
I don't follow you.
My clients typically fall
into two groups.
Some clients confess
and cooperate.
And some want to go free
without a drop of blood
on their hands.
(Missing Person)
If you didn't recognize him,
you would have looked closer.
You glanced away quickly,
so you know this person.
Is the new witness connected
to this missing person case?
If your lawyer does not know
what the prosecution knows,
it is a lost cause.
I need to know everything
to rebut the witness's testimony.
Tell me.
If you waste time like this,
you will surely be arrested.
It was two months ago.
Hi, honey.
- Where are you?
- Busan.
Is everything fine?
Conferences are all the same.
Discussions, meetings...
You sound tired.
It will go fine.
Dad does not say it,
but he expects a lot.
Doesn't he expect a grandchild
more than anything?
How about talking face-to-face?
Are you coming
to the opening today?
Are the preparations going well?
Don't deflect my question.
You will be back later, right?
Hello?
Sorry, what did you say?
When will you leave?
As soon as I finish up here.
Hurry, I miss you.
Miss you too.
Going already?
It is late.
Stay a bit longer.
You are not sober yet.
Drive for me, will you?
The two of you came here?
We had no other place
to go unnoticed.
Se-hee liked it here,
but I was uncomfortable.
- What?
- My bracelet.
I left it at the lodge.
I will get it next time.
- Turn right.
- Not the main road?
It is a shortcut.
And no cameras.
What is wrong?
I am tired.
Tired of lying.
You are honest with me.
I have to lie to everyone
except you.
Do you remember what we said
when we first met?
Just being together is enough.
Think like that.
One can't have everything.
Then can you choose?
I am not interested in marriage.
So what we have is perfect.
Do you want to end it?
Let's do that.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I am okay.
Hello?
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
- We should report it.
- Wait!
There was nothing we could do.
He was texting,
not wearing a seatbelt.
What does that matter?
The accident was our fault.
We did not hit him!
- He hit the boulder.
- So what?
You and I are not supposed
to be here now.
If you call the cops,
we are finished.
Nobody saw it.
We can just keep driving.
- Don't be absurd!
- Listen.
All you have accomplished...
Your family.
Your family!
What about them?
Huh?
Let's go.
- Why won't it start?
- Come on!
Please, just...
Hold on.
Wait.
What are you doing?
We are discussing the accident.
- I am that car's driver.
- What?
- Just follow my lead.
- You...!
Oh my...
Seems you had an accident?
An elk jumped out on the road.
Our cars skidded.
Does nobody hurt?
No, we are fine.
Sounds like your phone is ringing.
Must be the insurance company.
(Gwon Min-jun)
Are you sure you are okay?
A bit startled, but fine.
Well, then...
Yes, please do that.
As quickly as possible.
All set now.
That is a relief.
Drive safely.
Yes, thank you.
Are you sure
the witness did not see the body?
I was not there,
so I can only trust
what Se-hee said.
The license plate?
I did not see it.
Is the prosecution's new witness
that truck driver?
Right now it seems likely.
Go, quickly.
And you?
I will figure something out.
As you said, we didn't hit him.
We can still report it.
Get rid of this car,
and it is finished.
And we are finished.
Just as you wanted.
I was plagued by regret.
I should not have gone that way.
If I had gone left,
there would have been no accident.
Nothing would have happened.
I remembered what Se-hee said.
He is already dead.
He has no future,
but we do.
And then?
After ditching the car,
I met Se-hee again.
What is wrong?
What?
For roadside repair,
please approve the use
of location data.
Your call may be recorded...
Excuse me.
Are you having trouble?
I skidded to avoid an elk,
but now it won't start.
- Didn't you get hurt?
- No, I am fine.
Did you call for help?
Not yet.
They said it would take a while.
I can take a look.
Want to open the hood?
I run a car repair shop.
- Just a minute.
- Okay.
It is my sister's car.
There is a lever down
on the left.
Oh, right...
Just a minute.
Don't see anything wrong.
The ECU must have re-set.
Cars have so much electronics,
one error can shut them down.
How about coming to my house?
I will plug in a scanner
and fix the settings.
Or should I call a tow truck?
How long will it take?
- The tow truck?
- No. To fix it.
With travel time,
an hour should do it.
Please do that, then.
Here.
(Sehyun Auto Center
Han Young-seok)
You are not from around here?
Neither am I.
We moved here
when my wife got sick.
We did all the chemotherapy,
but the treatment is worse
than the disease.
She got better
after moving here, though.
She is even started working again.
- That is great.
- Yes.
Producer Lee?
Se-hee, how is the video coming?
I finished editing
and uploaded it to the cloud.
Then when are you coming?
The thing is...
Something came up.
I will go as fast as I can.
Do you work in video?
Yes.
I met my wife
at a broadcasting company.
She was a local news reporter,
and I drove the broadcast van.
Basically, I was her manager.
I took care of clothes,
makeup, even her meals,
so she just said,
let's just get married!
She is the type to make up
her mind in five seconds.
If she had not gotten sick,
she would be a news anchor
by now.
(Automobile Communication System
in progress)
Let's take a look.
Oh my, I woke you.
It is all fixed now.
Just a minute!
- How much do I...?
- No, no, no.
Just consider it a favor.
Sorry, I did not get you anything.
Have some chrysanthemum tea.
No, I am fine.
It won't take a minute.
Bring it with you.
My son dried the tea himself.
Perfect weather for it.
That boy put off college
and got a job for himself.
Growing up with a sick mother,
I guess he wanted to stay close.
My wife will be home soon.
Join us for dinner.
Just a minute.
Hi, Min-jun.
Sure, how have you been?
(Award for Broadcast Reporter
of the Month)
How are your parents?
Give my best regards to them.
Sun-jae?
Of course, he left.
He left right away.
Didn't he show up?
And he is not answering the phone?
That is strange.
Let me call you back.
Hello?
(Dad)
Look, he forgot
to take his phone!
I will be going now.
But...
Then what do we do now?
I have an idea.
But I can't do it myself.
Se-hee told me about her plan.
I could not believe
she came up with it so quickly.
Felt like a plan hatched
over a lifetime.
The look in her eye scared me.
We promised that would be
our last meeting,
and left.
Lastly, let's watch the video
that we prepared.
Thanks for coming to the opening
of the Haseon Art Gallery.
Did you hear it all?
You did great.
We succeeded somehow,
but I worried it could fall apart
in an instant.
What?
Do you want to junk the car?
It is at the construction site.
Make sure it can't be traced.
Why there?
It was a simple accident.
Just don't want trouble.
Anything else?
Just the car?
Do that for me.
Scrapping it will leave a record,
better to strip
and export it.
If we use a professional,
they won't cause trouble
because they are illegal, too.
I am your lawyer.
If you need anything, say it.
And just focus on the deal.
There was no more trouble,
but I could not rest from work.
I was preparing to export
my security program to China.
The fate of the company depended
on it.
Make sure it can't be traced.
Don't worry.
There are many concerns
with your proposal.
Your software is too expensive,
long development period,
maintenance issue in China.
And the most important thing,
your software is not verified!
(You have a visitor
from the police station.)
Sir. It is totally cost-effective.
We will create and build
this system as soon as possible.
Then you will be the very first
and the best in China.
At 5:40 p.m. on that day,
Han Sun-jae drove out
to meet a friend,
and disappeared.
His car vanished as well.
The boy's father stopped
on his way home to tow
and fix a car
that had broken down.
He said a woman was driving it.
Some parts that were found
where the car broke down matched
Han Sun-jae's missing car.
At the very spot
where the father towed her car,
there are signs
that a car struck a boulder.
But strangely enough,
no accident was reported.
So?
What does an incident in Gangwon
have to do with us?
The site of Han's accident...
You said he is missing.
You can't assume it was him.
His presumed accident matches
the location of that woman.
And the boy's father remembers
the car's license plate.
A search showed that
the car belongs to this company.
Mostly driven by you, sir.
Any employee can drive
a company car.
And I told you.
It was stolen.
We reported you the day after
our CEO came back from Busan.
What were you doing in Busan?
There was a conference.
And about the license plate,
we can't be sure the father
remembered correctly, can we?
Can we see records
on the use of the company car?
How about we stop?
Or you can get a warrant.
Don't you want
to find your stolen car?
The Transportation Division will
find it.
It is not your jurisdiction,
so don't pull in my client
without evidence.
We are busy,
so why don't you go?
We will go.
The car looked fine.
Why so nervous
about a tiny incident?
I was only in Busan
on the first day.
What about the second day?
With that woman?
You will need an alibi, then.
And the missing person?
Any connection?
Find a truck for me.
Know the license number?
I just know the model, color,
and driver's face.
That will take time.
What about the police?
You saw them.
They still can't touch you.
So I got an alibi,
and no more contact
from the police.
I thought it was over,
then the real nightmare started.
Daddy wants to go on a trip,
where should we go?
I am glad to go anywhere,
you decide.
Let's see...
The missing person case
of Han Sun-jae is now
a public investigation.
Gangwon police and residents are
combing the area,
but the mountainous terrain is
making the search difficult.
They still have not found him.
Police say it may not be
a simple disappearance...
Right.
But they are waiting
for conclusive evidence.
Police are also tracing the
whereabouts of one woman.
She was seen
by the missing man's father,
and was driving a stolen vehicle
on that day.
Police are investigating
a possible link
to the missing person case.
This is Ma Jeong-pil
on the scene for YTN News.
Would you like some more wine?
Sure.
Are you crazy?
How dare you call this number?
Did you watch the news?
What is going on?
What?
Is it not a simple disappearance?
Why am I a suspect?
What did you tell the police?
Police saw signs of an accident,
but no one reported it,
so they are suspicious.
Who decided
to report the car stolen?
The car disappeared,
it would be strange not to.
Then you should have told me!
What is that?
His wallet. I removed it
while putting him in the trunk.
What should I do with it?
All you need is in there.
His ID, business card,
even credit cards.
Do you think it is possible?
Make it possible.
It is your specialty.
The accident could not be helped.
But that is a crime!
You hid the body.
Isn't that a crime?
What?
You feel safe
because the father didn't see you,
but I won't go down alone.
Never.
(Seoul Central District
Prosecutors' Office)
(Credit Card Transactions)
(Financial Transactions
of Suspicious Accounts)
I accessed criminal records
for a voice phishing case.
By fabricating transactions,
I made it look like it was linked
to the Han Sun-jae case.
Was this all Se-hee's idea?
You don't know her.
She is the type
who never gives up.
Han Sun-jae's case is being turned
into a criminal investigation.
(Criminal Investigation Opens)
Several days
before his disappearance,
a voice phishing organization made
suspicious deposits
into the bank account
of the missing man.
The police conducted a search
for the residence,
believing that Han had disappeared
on his own.
With the police investigating Han,
we were no longer under suspicion.
We concluded the deal,
and I was named
IT Businessman of the Year.
I was soaked with congratulations
and interview requests.
But it was all such a sham.
I felt sick inside.
Hello?
- Is Ms. Yang there?
- She is with me now.
She signed
the defense agreement?
No, not yet.
Tell her everything.
She is never lost a case.
Make sure
she signs the agreement.
All right.
And I think I found the truck.
Really? And the driver?
The truck was there,
but his house was empty.
The prosecution is certainly
moving fast.
What do you mean?
The prosecution's witness may be
that truck driver.
Witness?
The evidence they have is
a witness?
That is what Ms. Yang heard.
- Let me speak to her.
- Just a second, please.
It is Attorney Jang.
Hello?
Ms. Yang, thanks for your help.
Yes.
What is this about a witness?
I am trying
to find out the details.
I am not sure who...
- Hello?
Hello?
We were cut off.
So all the cards are on the table.
Two incidents.
Two bodies.
The police only know
Se-hee's murder,
so you are the only suspect.
They need to know about Han
to see other possibilities.
The third person hidden
in that room is surely connected
to Han Sun-jae.
Did you say you were blackmailed?
Sir!
- This came for you.
- Who sent it?
No sender is written.
The price of my silence is
$1 million in cash.
If you bring anyone,
or report this,
I will reveal your infidelity.
Mr. Yoo.
I can't listen anymore.
I understand
why you would call this blackmail
over infidelity.
Because you want to keep
the Han Sun-jae incident secret.
Answer one of three questions,
and I will believe it.
First, who called the cops
before the attack in the hotel?
- This is the police.
- Second,
why didn't the blackmailer
take the money?
Third, how did he leave
the closed room?
You can't answer.
So it is not convincing to say
it was a blackmail
over infidelity.
Forget creativity,
your logic is a mess.
Then what is your logic?
You say both
of you got the same threat?
Yes, but only I was asked
for money.
The way I view this incident...
Something is not right.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Do you think
the boy's father killed her?
Han Young-seok has
the clearest motivation.
What is his motivation?
Revenge.
Look at this.
My son made a call
before I met that woman.
She carried the phone
to my house.
There are no grounds
to see it as an accident.
And that woman was not alone.
There was a passenger.
You only saw her.
What is your evidence?
I told you!
She adjusted the car seat.
It was not her car!
It is my sister's car.
The car is not hers.
It belongs to D&T Security.
Sir.
I am begging you.
Please investigate, okay?
Han Sun-jae!
Sun-jae!
Everybody move!
We have the warrant
to search your home.
But...
Start with his room!
What is going on?
Your son may have been involved
in financial crimes.
My son?
Honey!
Sun-jae!
A parent who loses
a child is already a monster.
If the son is wrongly accused,
and he can't even find the body,
he might do anything.
Han Young-seok lost his faith
in the police,
so he prepared
to judge you directly.
The price of my silence is
$1 million in cash.
If you bring anyone,
or report this,
I will reveal your infidelity.
He would have been convinced
that he would not be suspected.
Because he knew
you would never talk
about his son's case.
That weakness was
what he targeted.
And he succeeded.
He made everyone think that you,
her illicit lover, killed Se-hee.
During the three days
of your questioning,
he watched over your lawyer.
And he checked all the ways
you might try to free yourself.
- Mr. Yoo, give us a comment!
- Mr. Yoo!
When your arrest warrant
was nullified,
he even came to see me.
(Missing Person)
So you already knew
what happened two months ago.
If so, I would not have wasted
our time.
But if we don't know how he got in
and out of that room,
It is all useless, isn't it?
Han Young-seok knows all
about you,
but you know nothing.
So you can't see the key
to that closed room.
These are the crime photos.
The key is outside the room,
not in it.
Do you recognize this person?
- No.
- Of course not.
You have never met
Han Sun-jae's mother.
She is even started working again.
Your guest has already gone up
to the room.
Would you like a second key?
Name: Lee Hee-jung.
She worked
at the hotel's front desk.
Now you understand?
Why they called you to that hotel?
Han Young-seok knew
you would both
recognize the accident scene.
The fact you came to the hotel was
half a confession.
The rest went according to plan.
Booking the room next
to the storage closet
was intentional.
(The woman has gone up)
Han Young-seok waited
for them in the closet.
Lee Hee-jung called the police.
And Han staged the crime
as the police were arriving.
We received a call.
Excuse me.
Is everything okay?
I heard a strange noise inside.
And he escaped the room
with his wife's help.
Help!
Hands up!
Don't move!
It was not me.
Don't move! Stay still!
Another person is here!
If you want to prove
you did not kill Se-hee,
you need to implicate
Han Young-seok.
So you can't help
but pull in the Han Sun-jae case.
The most incriminating thing is
the bank hacking...
It will be impossible
to prove it was me.
Good.
That day, you were not
in the car with Se-hee.
You were in Busan
as per your alibi.
Se-hee, who often drove your car,
had the accident
and covered it up herself.
Then she stopped calling.
So I become Se-hee's victim...
You saw her in the hotel
for the first time in two months,
and learned
about the Han Sun-jae incident.
If you had an accident in my car,
you should have told me!
Why didn't you say something?
What do I do now?
Is that possible?
The dead don't talk.
We need one more puzzle piece
to prove she acted alone.
Where is Han Sun-jae's car?
Still,
the truck driver saw me.
Testimony can't compete
with evidence.
We can refute his credibility.
The prosecutor won't sit still
during the appeal trial.
We make sure there is no appeal.
How?
We just need direct evidence
that Se-hee killed Han Sun-jae.
Then if Se-hee,
the only suspect, is dead,
the prosecutor can't indict.
It will be impossible
to prosecute the case.
They just need to find something
of hers or DNA.
But to plant it,
we need the car.
Isn't there another method?
To prove Se-hee did it herself.
You come up with one.
This is when I start doubting.
When my client keeps trying
to deceive me.
How am I deceiving you?
Are you telling the truth?
Yes.
You seemed to like the scenario
I imagined,
no matter how well you
defend a lie,
it will collapse in court.
Isn't it the truth?
Only you know that.
What if everything was reversed?
Reversed?
Removing Sun-jae's wallet,
and hacking the bank was
all your idea.
And what if she was the one
who wanted to break up?
Sorry.
The person driving was not Se-hee,
it was you.
Shall we go back to the start?
Hello?
Sorry, what did you say?
When will you leave?
As soon as I finish up here.
Hurry, I miss you.
You too.
If you took the lead in all this,
doesn't it fit better?
- What are you doing?
- We should report it.
Nobody saw it.
We can just keep driving.
If you call the cops,
we are both finished!
Get a grip!
What if this whole situation was
driven by you,
and Se-hee was the one
who tried to stop it?
(Medical Report)
These are psychiatric records
of Se-hee.
After the accident,
she suffered severe anxiety.
She could not take it anymore.
Police say it may not be
a simple disappearance,
but they are waiting
for conclusive evidence.
Police are also tracing
the whereabouts of one woman.
She was seen
by the missing man's father,
and was driving a stolen vehicle
on that day.
Police are investigating
the possibility of a connection
to the missing person case.
Let's meet now and talk.
I will go to you.
Are you crazy?
I told you not to call me.
Why am I a suspect?
What did you tell the police?
Hello.
This is my son.
Finally, she made up her mind.
If she can't bring back their son,
at least she can do
the right thing.
Hello?
Se-hee called the boy's father.
It was an accident.
Honey.
Promising she would find
the location of the son's body,
she begged for forgiveness.
I will tell you where your son is.
I am sorry.
Then, why didn't he report it
after getting Se-hee's call?
Proving a murder with nobody is
near impossible.
Han must have known...
That you would never say
where the body is.
That you would always
find a way out.
He just hoped
Se-hee might find out
the body's location.
But Ms. Yang.
Actually,
I was not passed out completely.
I saw him for sure
from that room.
Why didn't you say so before?
An attorney I have never met will
determine my fate.
I need to judge, too.
You never change.
It is my job to make you innocent,
but I can't do it
- if you lie.
- What lie?
This photo proves it.
This woman and her husband plotted
to get revenge on me.
What stronger evidence is there?
That woman is not
Han Sun-jae's mother.
She is just a hotel employee.
I don't know her either.
There was never a third person
in that room.
It was just you and Se-hee.
At one mention
of Han Sun-jae's mother,
you lie about seeing the father?
If you know all this,
why invent such a story?
I need to hear the truth
from your mouth.
I told you.
Not to contact me.
So why dream up this crap
to get me out here?
Otherwise you would never take
my calls.
So what is it?
What do you want?
Let's confess.
It is not as if we killed him.
Kim Se-hee...
You have really gone mad.
I called his parents.
I told them everything.
Tell them where the car is,
and ask forgiveness.
It was not Han Young-seok
who killed Se-hee.
I don't care what you do to me.
My mind is made up.
You killed Se-hee,
and trapped yourself
in that closed room.
You must have gone over it
several times in your mind.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you in there?
This is the police.
Open the door!
I won't let you.
Mr. Yoo.
Salvation is never painless.
And you are not
as smart as I am.
Admit it, and tell the truth.
Then everything will be easier.
I will help you.
Did you kill Kim Se-hee?
Yes.
I killed her.
Very well.
We will take a break,
then continue.
It will all be over soon.
We are almost there.
Then what about his real mother?
One thing I am sure of is that
she must feel
like she died herself.
You are back late.
But I can't reach Sun-jae.
Really?
Yeah. He forgot his phone
at home.
I am sure he is out having fun.
I am cold.
We have the warrant
to search your home.
What is going on?
Your son may have been involved
in financial crimes.
Honey!
I know
about your son's disappearance.
It was an accident.
I will find out where he is.
I am sorry.
I am truly sorry.
Breaking news.
The head of an IT company has been
arrested on suspicion of murder.
Police have requested an autopsy
on the slain woman's body,
while the suspect, Mr. Yoo,
vigorously denies the charges.
Who are you?
I will see you tonight.
Mom!
However hard I try,
I can't remember it.
What my son said
to me that morning...
It was the last time.
I could sense my son every day
when I woke up.
Whether he was home, or out...
Every single day.
But now I can't feel anything.
What do you want?
I know that it was an accident.
Whether coincidence or a mistake,
I won't demand anything.
But please... find my son.
These people
are not people
you can stand up to.
(I must meet
the client right away.)
(Some new evidence...)
Hello?
Are you ready?
Yes. I will leave right away.
(Manager Han)
It seems Attorney Jang is busy.
He will come after finishing up.
This way.
This was far for you to come
after an all-night interrogation.
I had to escape the press.
You have not escaped
the prosecution, though.
Police are stationed 5 minutes
from here.
Is coffee okay?
Did she sign
the defense agreement?
No, not yet.
That is what Ms. Yang heard.
Let me speak to her.
Hello?
What is this about a witness?
I am not sure who...
Hello?
Ms. Yang?
- Hello?
We were cut off.
So where were we?
You said we needed
material evidence to prove
that Se-hee killed the boy.
Right.
I have one of Se-hee's bracelets.
Good.
We will plant the evidence,
then tell the police the location
in an anonymous tip.
Tell Attorney Jang
to reinforce the Busan alibi.
The fact you concealed knowledge
of the crime will get
you probation at most.
Ms. Yang.
Doesn't probation mean guilty?
I want to be not guilty.
We will do our best.
But first
we need to plant the evidence.
Where is the car?
Sunk in a lake.
With the body?
Yes.
There are many lakes
in that area.
Where exactly?
But what if that truck driver has
some kind of evidence?
Then we would be revealing
the location for nothing.
The prosecution has no witnesses.
What?
Any witness would have come
forward two months ago.
I made it up
to get your confession faster.
Then, rushing over here
because of the prosecutor...
That was a lie too?
We saved time,
and discovered a way
to prove you innocent.
You agree to defend me, right?
Now that you are
officially my lawyer,
you are bound
by confidentiality, right?
There is one thing
I have not told you.
I thought he was dead.
Really.
Save me!
What are you saying?
It was too late to turn back.
When it was over,
I could not find the wrench.
I searched,
but it must have
ended up in the trunk.
Please take care of it.
When you plant the evidence,
get rid of the wrench.
You said it was an accident.
By then it was too late anyway.
How could you...?
I know it is difficult,
but please help me.
Did you say he was alive?
You could have saved him.
Despite your excuses,
you are a murderer.
You said you wanted the truth.
So you can defend me.
You don't deserve one bit
of help.
- What?
- You killed two people.
If people find out,
you are finished!
Shut up!
You are my lawyer now.
So do your damn job.
Got it?
(I know where Sun-jae...)
Ms. Yang?
Yes?
I am sorry for shouting.
Our contract is still valid,
right?
Of course.
I can't break confidentiality,
or it will leave a black mark
on my career.
Let me formally request your help.
Which lake is it?
Is that correct?
Yes.
Very well.
I will arrange
to plant the evidence right away.
(Attorney Yang Shin-ae)
Just a minute.
Sorry, you scared me.
You won't get out that way.
I will get you chains.
Come wait inside.
Where did I put them?
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
How did you get
to know the Chairman?
Through a lawsuit, of course.
Really?
I heard you were
from the same hometown.
That too.
I mean, we first met in court...
Ah, there they are.
Would you bring me that stool?
Thank you.
You lie, too.
The Chairman's hometown is
in North Korea.
Who are you?
Lee Hee-jung.
The mother of the man you killed.
Then that makes sense.
That boy did nothing wrong.
You went too far.
So did you.
Your theory of Se-hee shocked me.
Almost perfectly accurate.
That is when I decided
I could put my fate in your hands.
Then you should have practiced
the signature.
So what is it?
What do you want from me?
Do you want an apology?
No, just let me find him.
That map?
I almost told you for real, but...
You were acting so strange.
Right, both of us were unlucky.
It was an accident, as you said.
I won't bother you anymore.
You can't just leave.
- Wait!
- Let go of me!
Hello?
This is Mount 23.
Help,
someone is trying to kill me.
Come quickly.
Do you think you are smarter
than me?
What is more important is
to survive.
We have a shooting incident.
Please send an ambulance.
Hello?
This is Mount 23.
Help,
someone is trying to kill me.
Come quickly.
That is everything.
We got the call,
and a nearby police car came.
We arrested Lee Hee-jung
with the gun in her hands.
How is he?
The wound is not serious.
The road conditions are bad,
so we will treat him here first.
I don't want to see
those people ever again.
Don't worry.
Attempted murder is a felony.
Even for a first offense,
it is serious.
What about the recording
from their car?
Whatever you said,
illegal wiretapping can't be used
as evidence in court.
Contrarily, the recording shows
you are a victim.
The police will visit you
in the hospital.
But don't worry.
I will take care of it all.
Just a minute!
Good news!
What is it?
That truck driver passed away.
A month ago.
Is it crude,
calling that good news?
They said
the prosecution has no witness.
Really?
How is Attorney Yang?
She is the best.
Could not be better.
That is what we want.
Thanks for your help.
The patient's condition seems
good.
You have only made things
more complicated.
Can you handle it?
You came too far.
We should have stopped
at the rest stop.
Yoo Min-ho...
Don't defend him.
I say this as my apology to you.
You will lose for sure.
Stop!
Slowly, slowly!
Come forward!
- Go ahead.
- Ambulance, stand by!
Confirmed.
Yoo Min-ho came here
for a reason.
Attorney Yang says she will go
directly to your cabin.
All right.
This was far for you to come
after an all-night interrogation.
I had to escape the press.
He had something to do here.
When it was over,
I could not find the wrench.
What do you mean?
My son...
I think I know where he is.
A place where no one
would stumble across it.
A place only he knows.
Sunk in a lake.
This is private property!
It is also a crime scene.
Criminal code,
article 216, clause 1.
A crime scene can be searched
without a warrant.
Diving team, access
from behind the cabin.
Other search teams,
you can enter the property.
Cabin team, go ahead.
Everybody move!
(Yoo Min-ho)
Found it!
You are under arrest
for the murder of Han Sun-jae.
Mr. Yoo.
Salvation is never painless.
Admit it, and tell the truth.
I will help you.